The film you are about to see was born under the sound of the stars .
To our makers Who are no longer with us
You have seen a film based on real events that happened in France in winter 1996
Existence is a fleeting illusion
What does dance mean to you ?
Everything .
Dance is everything .
It 's all I have .
If you couldn 't dance , what would you do ?
Suicide .
When you 're on stage dancing ...
you feel free , no barriers ,
no judgement .
Just us , our body and sensations .
I find marijuana is a great muscle relaxant .
So when you dance the sensations are a bit different ,
you 're more sensitive ...
with certain muscles , or sensations .
When I dance , I can be someone
I can 't be anywhere else .
OK .
Is your family supportive ?
Yes .
Mum , dad , everyone ...
They know what you dance ?
Yes .
Do they come to watch ?
No .
I prefer not .
What would they say ?
They 'd be a bit shocked .
Would you do anything to make it ?
Meaning ?
You 're in a profession where ...
you need to bring enjoyment ...
I 'm ready for anything .
What 's anything ?
Everything .
I don 't know what you 'll ask me to do
but I 'm primed
and honestly , it 's a chance in a million
to work with a choreographer like you .
It could really help me evolve ,
so I 'm ready for anything .
I can ask you anything ?
Anything .
My worst nightmare ?
To find myself alone .
With nothing and no one around .
Alone .
Do you have a life motto ?
" What doesn 't kill you makes you stronger . "
Do you believe in paradise ?
Yes .
Why ?
Because I want to .
What 's in paradise ?
Everything good .
Meaning ?
Only good things , no problems .
There 's no chaos there .
I am from Berlin ,
but I 'm happy to leave .
It became too much . The art scene there is too much
I really want to do what I love ,
without ... being fucked up .
There 's a lot of drugs in Berlin . It 's too much .
My ex-roommate , I don 't talk to him anymore ...
Before I moved out , he started to take acid in his eyes .
Like actual drops .
So I decided to get away from all that , because ...
I don 't want to end up like Christiane F.
I like to let off steam ...
I have my secret garden that I ...
I like to go to when I party .
I tried a line of coke once .
You asked me to be open so ...
Yeah , I snorted a line with a girlfriend .
My worst nightmare ?
I 'm real scared of darkness .
Really scared .
You know , when you do your own thing ,
it 's make or break .
And in my experience , it 's mostly break .
I wade right in .
If there 's a problem , I deal with it then move on .
What 's the worst you 've done to a guy in a fight ?
I smashed a head once .
Knocked two of his teeth out .
He had a big gash in his forehead .
He passed out .
Two days in a coma .
Do you regret it ?
Not really . That 's life .
Do you do drugs ?
No , never .
No drugs . I 'm more into girls .
What do you think of the other dancers ?
Some look good .
It all seems good .
Meaning ?
Some of the girls are hot .
Your cousin 's your partner in crime ?
Yeah , we pick up girls together .
And guys ?
Guys , well ...
Guys ... it depends .
Straight up , I 've never worked with gays before .
I 'm a little nervous , but ...
it 's no big deal ...
I 'm just waiting for the first connection .
I 've heard things but want to see for myself .
For sure , I 'm a bit nervous about it .
But I like that , feeling the fear .
Being brother and sister , we 're close of course ,
but with dance we share an activity that ...
keeps us close .
We 'll be touring France and the States .
What do you think ?
I 've been to New York so ...
Wow , that 's awesome !
We 've never been to the US together .
Yes , I 've been to New York .
Oh ?
With who ?
The US is the place to go .
And for black culture too , it 's great .
America ?
America ...
it 's heaven on earth .
You 've been there ?
Never .
I come from hell .
Where is hell ?
We 're lucky in France to really shine in dance .
It 's incredible .
It would be interesting to take that to other countries ,
like America or places where ...
the level 's not so high .
France is a country that really has our back ,
helping us , with its culture ,
and music ,
which really lets us ...
flourish and ...
work with a level of excellence .
It 's the French trademark .
PRESENT A FRENCH FILM AND PROUD OF IT
God is with us !
Now let 's party !
I love your kid !
My Tito .
Great dancer !
Can I dance with him ?
Go ahead . I made some sangria .
Later .
What did you think ?
Awesome !
Maybe just the two girls in the middle ...
Totally get it .
We 'll rehearse it later .
Everyone 's tired , they wanna have fun .
Sure , it 's tough .
For just 3 days ' work , it was fabulous .
What are you discussing ?
You ! Come talk with me .
Yo , David !
You do this every time !
Sangria ?
I don 't drink .
Oh sure .
You know it .
Cool .
Drink ?
No , thanks .
Sure ?
I don 't feel good .
Here .
Thanks .
What do you want ?
I told you to stop .
I told you yesterday , please .
No one 's looking , OK ?
Happy now ?
I wanna be with you .
When ?
I 'm here now .
Go dance !
You ! You !
That solo , every single time , it 's so good !
Thank you .
- You 're so good . - You liked it ?
I couldn 't be happier . Thank you guys , you 're amazing .
You ...
Sorry !
Don 't worry .
I love your attitude .
Thanks .
You and Omar have something going ...
Say what ?
Great rehearsal , huh ?
Yeah .
I got my eye on you , watch out .
Hey Daddy , great track !
Up for a drink ?
No .
She 'd like one .
Thanks .
Why so glum ?
I 'm not , I 'm just tired .
Stop sulking !
I 'm tired !
You 're always tired !
Help me down ?
No sweat .
It 's sangria I made for the dancers .
It 's alcohol , it 's not good for you .
It 's not juice .
Alcohol .
Give the kid a break !
Come dance with me , Tito !
Dance with me !
Pump it up , Daddy !
How was it ?
Great !
As usual .
What 's up ?
Remember our dance ?
This way , then like this ...
Then like that .
Can I have a hug ?
And another ?
One more ?
How hard can you laugh ?
Where 's your mom ?
I 'm gonna get changed .
What was the deal earlier ?
What ?
With your bro .
You know your pal Taylor ...
He 's afraid I 'll get pregnant .
Chill .
Down the hatch .
No .
It stinks , why drink it ?
David !
Selva ...
I 'm worried about the boy .
Why ?
He 's gone to bed , he 's fine .
Something wrong ?
Nothing at all .
This is not a good place for a kid .
Leave it out .
He 's fine .
He 's happy , good mannered .
No .
Yes , she 's raised him well .
She was right to not abort him .
Wicked sangria !
Wicked !
Have you ever had an abortion ?
It 's good to have the choice .
Don 't you think ?
BIRTH IS A UNIQUE OPPORTUNITY
You know mummy was a dancer .
When I see you ,
I see myself as a little girl .
I hope you 'll be a dancer , like mummy .
Yes .
Have you spent 3 nice days here ?
We don 't see each other much , do we ?
Today I made an effort .
I 'm a good mummy ?
Yes .
Give me a kiss .
Close your eyes , go to sleep .
Sleep now .
I 'll be back later , because I love you .
I love you , Tito .
That flag over there ...
It freaks me out .
I don 't like it .
I like all flags .
The colours and all , it 's cool .
But this one ... I 've seen it too much .
Change of scenery , please !
Those crosses are creepy , man .
Chill , it 's not contagious .
Don 't be a prick .
God is great .
" God is with us . "
Since when have God and dance gone together ?
That 's not it .
I 'm not OK with it .
And you ?
Still the same .
Your dad ?
Still in a coma .
So we wait .
How long now ?
Almost 6 months .
Long time .
Yep .
If you 're down it 's complicated ,
if you ask me ...
to take drugs ... just ...
in a safe place .
And with my boyfriend I thought ...
it was safe .
Sorry ?
I thought it was safe
to take it ,
but you never know where it comes from .
See that babe ...
I fucked her yesterday .
Yesterday , bro .
Oh yeah ... !
And she 's crap .
So I wanna fuck two blondes .
Stop acting like I don 't exist .
You 're so fuckin ' fake .
I 'm not fake , you 're boring .
Dyke stuff never works .
They need cock .
For sure .
Both of them together , fuck it !
You asked about me marrying . Do you want kids ?
No , fuck that , I never think about it .
People ask these dumb questions .
" Watch out , he 's like this or that , "
I don 't give a shit .
There 's a connection ,
I take it , I live it , period !
I move on .
What a coke fiend !
Always snorting .
It stinks . Stinks .
You said you want to get married ?
Yes .
I heard right ?
How many times ?
Once !
Just once .
I 'd like to marry 4 times .
Best to do it often .
Change the game , the person , everything ...
How does she do it , at her age ?
Honestly ...
he must totally manipulate her .
He 's hungry .
He 's tried to screw us all .
A climber . Why 's he with the boss lady ?
To go places .
He 's with everyone .
With her he 's just looking for work .
We hit lucky here ...
Bro ! Omar !
Wake up !
Get out of your trip !
You don 't drink , you do nothing .
I 've boned them all here .
All of them .
David ? He 's a ticket to an STD .
That 's mean .
He 's my buddy !
He 's nice , but ...
He should ...
I bet he has herpes .
He 's dirty .
Just the way he looks at you ...
Cut it out !
It can be a turn-on .
Ok , he 's a sonofabitch !
He has his charms .
Is he a good lay at least ?
A top shooter !
Sometimes they make out like ...
No , really !
Have you two screwed ?
No , but he 's banged someone next to me .
A young chick ...
You gang bang ?
He fucked her brains out .
Tell me about Gazelle .
Just a little .
I 'm curious .
Please ?
Just a little , no details if she 's ass or pussy .
Just ... how nuts she goes .
You live your life , I live mine .
Your life is mine as well .
Get off my case .
I don 't get it , I 'm reacting ...
No , I don 't see why you react like that .
What makes Omar special ?
Everything .
Oh yeah ?
He 's got everything !
Know what ?
I wanna bone her .
I 'm not surprised .
Honestly , I wanna bone her .
You 're a lucky man .
You 're not as tough as me .
So , let 's ask her .
Maybe we can do a threesome ?
You say : " It 's the last night ,
" everything sucks ,
" the sex ...
" it 's not like before ...
" Nowadays , group sex is the thing , all that stuff . "
And we do it .
What bugs you ?
Seeing you together .
I don 't like him .
We may seem buddies but we 're not .
So what ?
I 'm your big brother .
I 'm 20 , not a baby anymore .
So ?
You disrespect me .
He seems totally uptight .
Only with you !
Say what ?
What it says .
You 're not my mum or dad .
Just my big brother .
So ?
You 're 25 . I 'm 20 , an adult .
But you 're ...
still too young for that .
For what ?
What you do with Omar .
You know what we do ?
I see enough .
No need for details .
You 've had your dick sucked already .
So ?
That doesn 't mean you can suck his ...
any time you like !
That 's not how it goes .
It 's normal when you 've been together 9 months , no ?
9 months , you two ?
He didn 't tell you ?
No .
Think it 's funny ?
This place has seen some weird shit .
I can feel it ,
sacrifices ... strange shit , for sure .
You mean like a sect ?
All that stuff .
How can you walk in a room and see a flag like that ?
No way .
No way !
I don 't dig the vibe in this group .
They 're weird .
And this school ...
intensifies it .
It magnifies the sense of weirdness .
Weird or not ...
I 'll fuck them all !
Straight up !
Weird or not , I fuck them .
True ...
Even if the ghost turns up .
On the flag !
We 'll fuck him on the flag !
Ghost or no , he 'll get some !
I 'm sick of all the fathers and brothers
on our case all the time , telling us what to do .
Who you can or can 't see . Enough already .
There 's more to life than men .
Too right .
There are girls ...
nice ones too , huh ?
Like who ?
Some cute ones in the group .
Don 't you think ?
Like me ?
You know already , I told you .
So why bring it up ?
I 'm not , it just came up ...
You 're up for some filthy shit , man .
Hell , yeah .
I 'm gonna beat those two up tonight .
They deserve it .
Too true .
I 'm getting a real good vibe now ...
Real good !
I 'm ready for some crazy shit !
You 're too unstable , that 's your trouble .
Learn to keep it in your pants .
You only live once , bro .
When it 's long like mine ...
you gotta use it .
It 's a gift !
I gotta share it .
I bet they do it with strap-ons .
I don 't dig that shit .
I 'd fuck Psyche good .
So good .
When she does her wacko workout thing , I love it !
On the floor .
On the floor ! Straight in !
Bare knees !
No lube .
Wet or not , I keep at it !
I keep at it anyway !
You keep at it . You slap her !
No other way .
It 's party time !
A babe like that ?
When I stick my cock in , it goes all the way up to her throat .
I don 't stop till she weeps .
Till she weeps !
Gotta make her weep !
I love her .
Despite her flaws , her mistakes ...
So you 'll get back with her ?
I 'd like to .
Too bad she 's pregnant .
It 's someone else 's .
Her " sweet butterfly , " she says .
She 's pregnant ?
Yes .
By another guy ?
Imagine ...
your dream man ...
in love with someone else .
Lou , she 's hot .
Think she takes it up the ass ?
Hell yeah , all the way !
Deep inside .
Dry or with lube ?
Dry , man !
You grab her ,
spread her arms ...
Badass !
That 's how it goes !
Dry .
Dry !
No jelly .
I hate that stuff .
I prefer shea butter .
It 's the real deal .
Slides right in .
You have to pull her hair , for sure .
The basics .
I bang her .
I fuck her .
I 'm telling you ...
that girl ...
She 's a big deal .
Give it to her good !
Nice sweet ass .
Fuck her real good .
Then again ... no sweat .
Sure .
Selva 's my pick .
When she walks that way I wanna bang her .
When she talks or looks at you ...
Showing off .
It 's too much .
I get it .
You gotta show her who 's ...
Gonna show her what I got ...
An anaconda !
That chick ...
One day , after rehearsal ...
you follow her upstairs ...
you follow her .
You show her .
Just show her !
Show it to her !
My willy ?
You know what .
She 'll freak out .
That 's life , man !
I stick it straight in her ass .
No waiting .
Straight in .
In the ass .
I 'm not annoyed , but you don 't listen .
It gets a little ...
I 'm sick and tired of it .
What ?
Waiting !
After a while , you know ...
It 's best to wait .
You 're young . You 're rich .
You 'll get plenty of cock .
Sicko !
No need to do it all right now .
Take your time , be different .
I bet David will take two days .
David will never go with you .
You 'll see ...
Selva won 't let him .
Screw Selva .
I don 't know if you get it , but ...
who gives a fuck about Selva ?
Who is she , anyway ?
Get me David and wham bam it 's done .
Do as you like .
You always do .
That 's what I said I 'd do !
Yep ! That 's why you 're still a virgin .
Not for long !
With David , for sure !
He 's clearly a virgin .
It 's gotta happen .
He gotta get his butthole split .
Nice and wide .
With a baton .
A big one .
You know the score : first they squeal ,
then they 're happy and want more .
I won 't touch no butthole , man .
Butthole 's not my thing .
Smells of shit .
Oh , come on !
No butts .
Know what you do ?
You lick it .
What ?
The butthole !
Crazy !
Lick it good .
Stick your tongue in .
Even when it stinks ?
Don 't worry , man .
It 's nature !
You kidding ?
Occupational hazard , bro .
You 've had a babe poop on you ?
No , but hey ...
Shit happens !
Occupational hazard !
It 's a risk , you go down there ,
you know what you 'll find .
If you find it , don 't act surprised .
No way , man ...
It 's double or quits . In , out , in , out ...
I 've put Tito to bed , I 'm worn out .
Gimme a smoke .
He 's a cute kid .
You start dancing young , you 're hot to trot .
And then ...
You get screwed in some corner ,
then you get pregnant .
So what do you do ?
You have to make your big mistakes
a success .
I don 't even know what time the van 's coming tomorrow .
And everyone 's dancing happily .
The only thing I 've ever done right is this sangria .
It 's real good .
That 's it .
This is for France , guys !
Let 's slaughter those yanks !
Slaughter them !
This is War !
Brought you :
Dancing to music by :
Filmed by :
It 's hot in here !
Booty parade !
- Lou , do you want my glass ? - No thanks .
You know what ? The sangria is halal .
Oh shit .
I feel weird .
Go drink some water .
Selva .
Gimme some coke .
Huh ?
Some coke .
None left .
Ask the druggy .
Gimme some coke , babe .
I 'm all out .
I heard you had some .
It 's all gone .
All cool ?
I 'm cool . Gimme a light .
Daddy , look !
Look ... !
Over there .
What are you doing ?
Gazelle !
I 'm burning !
Something 's kicking in .
Gazelle !
I 'm off .
Bravo !
Way to party !
What 's going on ?
We 're partying , chill .
Go dance and have fun , you earned it .
Dance , baby !
What have you done ?
What do you mean ?
I haven 't done anything .
Selva !
I 've done nothing .
What 's wrong ?
I don 't know .
She 's feeling sick ?
Selva ?
You OK ?
You 're all too drunk , I 'm going to bed .
What 's up ? Feel sick ?
Selva ?
Don 't you guys feel weird ?
What 've you done ?
What did you put in the sangria ? I don 't feel good .
What are you talking about ?
What ? I haven 't done anything .
What 've you done ?
What 's wrong with you all ?
Daddy !
That bitch spiked our drinks !
The sangria 's spiked , it 's not me , I drank it too .
So that 's why I feel bad .
It 's not me .
What did you put in it ?
Here 's the bitter slut .
I drank it too !
Stop !
Hear her out !
It must be someone who didn 't drink it .
I know who it is . It 's Omar , the sonofabitch !
It 's not him !
Why haven 't you drunk it ?
You spiked it with LSD ?
It 's not him !
Why did you do it ?
He drugged us !
It 's him !
Stop , stop !
Get out !
Stop !
Asshole !
Open up !
Let me go !
Is LSD acid ?
I don 't know !
What 's the remedy ?
Coke .
Hand it over , we need it .
I 'm out , fuck off !
It 's not you ?
No .
Are you sure ?
We 're all fucking high .
We 're all fucking high , can 't you see ?
You OK ?
No , can 't you see ?
Did you see your son ?
Fuck !
Don 't drink that !
You mustn 't .
Come on !
No , mummy !
They 're all crazy in here !
Mummy , no !
Calm down !
Stop tugging !
Come on , stop that !
Mummy ...
No ...
No , mummy , you 're mean !
I love you !
I 'm doing it to protect you .
You 're mean !
Listen , listen to me .
Don 't touch that !
Don 't touch it !
It 'll kill you if you touch it .
No , mummy !
Don 't leave me alone !
Open the door !
I can 't !
I 'll be back , I 'll sort it out .
I 'll be back , don 't worry .
I 'll be back .
I love you . Calm down , please .
What are you doing ?
Protecting him from you !
From who ?
All of you !
Go fuck yourself !
Dumb bitch !
Useless cunt !
Selva ?
Selva !
I 'm talking to you .
Do you hear me ?
I need you .
I 'm sorry .
What 's wrong ?
I don 't feel good .
You drank too ?
No , I didn 't .
So why do you feel sick ?
Are you ok ?
The sangria 's been spiked by Emmanuelle .
I don 't know ...
What 's wrong with you all ?
Why do you feel sick ?
Can you keep a secret ?
Yes .
Always .
Selva .
Can you keep one for me ?
Please ?
Of course .
I have ...
I have something growing in my tummy .
Like what ?
I 'm pregnant , Selva !
Shit .
Yep .
What 'll you do ?
I don 't know .
Who 's the dad ?
No idea .
I don 't know .
I 'm wasted ...
You gals too ?
I 'm fine .
You 're alright ?
Could you leave us ?
Why ?
She 's weird .
You didn 't drink ...
No , she didn 't ...
She feels sick .
Me too .
Could you please just ...
Strange , why didn 't you drink ?
I feel sick , it happens !
You drugged us , huh ?
No !
She didn 't .
Dom , please !
You drugged us .
Not true !
You 're talking shit !
Are you nuts ?
You drugged us .
Go dance with the crew .
I threw Omar out for nothing ...
Because of you .
Why didn 't you drink ?
She 's pregnant !
Wait a sec , please !
You 're pregnant ?
Pregnant , you lying bitch ?
Lying cunt !
Bitch !
Whore .
Call an ambulance !
Will somebody help me ?
Lou ?
What 's wrong , Lou ?
What happened ?
Oh God ...
You 're such a bitch !
You had some all along .
So gimme some .
Get off me .
Lou !
Wait !
Go away !
Dom !
I 'll kill you !
Mummy !
There are cockroaches !
It 's a nightmare !
A nightmare .
What 's going on ?
What 's going on in here ?
Dom !
Someone ...
Do you want to see my anaconda ?
Where is Dom ? Where is Dom ?
Hey Taylor !
Check out your sister .
Check her out !
What are you doing ?
Why did you do that ?
She hit me !
Look !
We kicked the wrong guy out .
It wasn 't Omar , it 's her !
She poisoned us .
You drugged us ?
Yes she did .
What do you mean ?
Know what ?
She claims she 's pregnant .
Who 's the dad ?
Who is it ?
Who wants you ?
You 're a liar !
Who fucked you ?
You 're pregnant so you didn 't drink ? !
You did it !
No !
Shut the fuck up !
What the fuck are you saying ?
What are you talking about ?
It 's the son of David !
Get off me !
Go for her !
You 're threatening me ?
What are you gonna do ?
Want to hit me again ?
She hit me !
Shut up !
Fuck off !
Do it !
I 'll make you abort !
Gazelle !
Go on , do it !
Do it !
Go on , kill yourself !
Go on !
Do it !
Stop !
Stop , please .
Gazelle !
Lou !
Stop it !
Get off me !
It 's not your fault .
Leave her !
Leave her , Eva !
You don 't get it , I don 't want to !
Let 's get outta here .
Come on Selva , we 're leaving .
Mummy !
Come on .
We 're leaving .
It 's out of control .
Stop crying , please .
We 'll leave together .
I 'll find the key .
I 'll find it , don 't worry .
Open the door .
I lost the key .
Go find it .
I lost it .
Go find it !
I 'm scared !
Open the door , I 'm scared .
Open the door .
Please !
Everything 's fine .
Something 's moving here !
It 's a party ...
There 's balloons and surprises ...
Mummy !
The keys must be here ...
Come here !
Motherfucker !
Shithead !
Bring him here .
Fuck him up !
Harder !
Slimy shit !
Gimme a knife !
I 'll circumcise him !
Get off him .
You 're sick .
Take that .
Don 't wanna play with me ?
What are you doing ?
Gimme that !
What ?
The lipstick !
That hurts !
Let go !
Let go , dammit .
Come here , fucker !
Thought you were badass ?
Huh , asshole ?
Piece of white shit !
Motherfucker !
Get off !
Help me , please ...
Please ...
Please !
Selva , come with me .
Shit ! Tito 's fried !
Oh God , I 've killed him !
I 've killed him !
Fried !
Tito !
Stop screaming !
Music !
It 's OK . I got my ghetto blaster !
I 'll put it on , don 't worry .
Open the door , Tito !
Open up !
What are you doing ?
The blood !
The blood ... the blood ...
Selva .
Get out ! Get out !
What do you want ? Why ...
What do you want ?
Get out .
I don 't want to see you any more .
I don 't want to see you !
Leave the girls be .
Baby , don 't cry !
My little baby .
Everything will be fine .
We 're home .
Daddy , I 'm scared .
What 's happening ?
We 're home .
Riley ?
Leave me alone !
Get out !
Just get out !
What 's going on ?
Get off !
Get the fuck out of here !
Gazelle !
Wait !
It 's too dangerous !
Wait up .
It 's far too dangerous !
I 'm gonna kill myself !
I just want to protect you .
I 'm coming , Tito !
Gazelle !
Hold me close .
You know we can 't do it .
Let go .
I 'm sorry , Gazelle .
Let me go .
Let 's go somewhere .
Look what you did to Omar .
Look what you did !
Say you love me .
Let me go !
Mummy !
What are you doing ?
I love you Gazelle .
I 'll tell mum and dad . Let me go !
I just want to go , please .
I love you .
No !
Gazelle !
Let go !
Help !
I 'm here , don 't scream .
Let go .
You 're a liar .
I 'm not , Gazelle . I love you .
You 're vile !
We 'll go where you want .
Let me be .
Wanna go to New York ?
Let go .
Only I can make you happy .
Everyone 's watching .
Not here !
What 's wrong ?
Hold me .
You 're my world .
Let 's go to the room .
To the room .
The room .
You 're everything to me .
Everything .
Please ...
Please !
Do it !
Life is a collective impossibility
Look here .
Lady ?
She 's gone .
Death is an extraordinary experience
Nothing happened ...
What ?
Nothing happened .
What do you mean ?
Don 't tell dad .